{
  "type": "rome2hira",
  "level": "SEION",
  "questions": [
    { "prompt": "a", "answer": "あ" },
    { "prompt": "i", "answer": "い" },
    { "prompt": "u", "answer": "う" },
    { "prompt": "e", "answer": "え" },
    { "prompt": "o", "answer": "お" },
    { "prompt": "ka", "answer": "か" },
    { "prompt": "ki", "answer": "き" },
    { "prompt": "ku", "answer": "く" },
    { "prompt": "ke", "answer": "け" },
    { "prompt": "ko", "answer": "こ" },
    { "prompt": "sa", "answer": "さ" },
    { "prompt": "shi", "answer": "し" },
    { "prompt": "su", "answer": "す" },
    { "prompt": "se", "answer": "せ" },
    { "prompt": "so", "answer": "そ" },
    { "prompt": "ta", "answer": "た" },
    { "prompt": "chi", "answer": "ち" },
    { "prompt": "tsu", "answer": "つ" },
    { "prompt": "te", "answer": "て" },
    { "prompt": "to", "answer": "と" },
    { "prompt": "na", "answer": "な" },
    { "prompt": "ni", "answer": "に" },
    { "prompt": "nu", "answer": "ぬ" },
    { "prompt": "ne", "answer": "ね" },
    { "prompt": "no", "answer": "の" },
    { "prompt": "ha", "answer": "は" },
    { "prompt": "hi", "answer": "ひ" },
    { "prompt": "fu", "answer": "ふ" },
    { "prompt": "he", "answer": "へ" },
    { "prompt": "ho", "answer": "ほ" },
    { "prompt": "ma", "answer": "ま" },
    { "prompt": "mi", "answer": "み" },
    { "prompt": "mu", "answer": "む" },
    { "prompt": "me", "answer": "め" },
    { "prompt": "mo", "answer": "も" },
    { "prompt": "ya", "answer": "や" },
    { "prompt": "yu", "answer": "ゆ" },
    { "prompt": "yo", "answer": "よ" },
    { "prompt": "ra", "answer": "ら" },
    { "prompt": "ri", "answer": "り" },
    { "prompt": "ru", "answer": "る" },
    { "prompt": "re", "answer": "れ" },
    { "prompt": "ro", "answer": "ろ" },
    { "prompt": "wa", "answer": "わ" },
    { "prompt": "wo", "answer": "を" },
    { "prompt": "n", "answer": "ん" }
  ]
}
